Mary Feiz



aalinoosh@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mary-feiz



+34629478050



http://www.aalinoosh.es/

Summary

Hi, I'm Maryam. A Web Developer with a thorough understanding of web compatibility, performance, usability, accessibility, maintainability. I Do my best to develop web products that offer users a great experience. I am always interested in playing around with new technologies but these are the ones that have really won me over

Skills:

Google AMP (Accelerated Mobile Pages) React, Redux, JSX HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS AMP, Responsive layout, Bootstrap progressive web apps, Chrome extensions

Webpack, Yarn, npm Git, GitHub, GitLab, Agile Page speed optimization, accessibility, SEO

UX / UI design, mockups, wireframes, prototypes Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch Back-end exposure: Node, Java, PHP, SQL

Master of Smart intelligence interactive systems, UPF University of Barcelona.

Experience



Researcher /Frontend Developer

1DES

May 2020 - Present (10 months +)

1DES is an automated crypto trading based on ML. I've designed, developed, and maintained 1Des.com.



Frontend Developer

DOTRAVEL Ltd

Dec 2017 - May 2020 (2 years 6 months)

working in a team on a "travelers platform". Architect, designed, developed, implemented, and launched the Dotravel website, I'm more focused on the Frontend part of it, leading and mentoring progress and implemented corrective actions. I've involved in content marketing, customer engagement, and community building strategies.



Freelance Web Developer

Consultant

Sep 2016 - May 2018 (1 year 9 months)

I worked as a consultant for several Accenture clients.

Built multilingual marketing pages for ecommerce project. Used XHTML, CSS and JavaScript.



Front End Developer, SEO manager, Digital Marketing Manager

Golrang Industrial Group

Sep 2009 - Apr 2016 (6 years 8 months)

- •SEO manager, drive web traffic and increase brand awareness
- code complex web apps (Java/ JavaScript)
- · architecture front-end project
- define project coding style guidelines and best practices
- · optimize page speed and web app performance
- test, debug, refactor legacy React/ JS/CSS/HTML

Accomplishments:

I have launched 7 Web-based projects & Storage software with GCMS framework



🛝 Project Manager

Pouzhman Saze Pars

May 2006 - May 2009 (3 years 1 month)

Project manager

As a Project Manager, my main role consists in leading Software integrated Solutions projects, focused on multichannel Retail Applications, as well as all kind of Audio Visual and sensory marketing projects worldwide for several Brands such as SOFTLAN, BARLIE, NANCY ... I was in charge of developing all Technical Project Documentation and analyzing with our customers how to get the most out of our Technical Solutions, all in order to provide the final customers the best shopping experience, based on our Sensory Marketing solutions knowledge.



UX/UI Designer and Developer

GATRIA

Dec 2003 - Dec 2006 (3 years 1 month)

Since I've started my career as UX/UI Designer, I have 3 years of experience at Gatria startup company as an Operations Manager and working with the Customer relationship management system, Since the second year, I worked on both Front End development and UX Design.

- · advise on front-end technologies and project architecture
- define project coding style guidelines and best practices
- assist front-end team formation, technical interviews, training
- · assist Scrum backlog and tickets definition
- design UI layouts in Sketch/Illustrator/Photoshop
- design UX with interactive mockups

Education



Universitat Pompeu Fabra

Master's degree, Intelligent interactive systems 2016 - 2018

Shahid Bahonar University of Kerman

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering

Shahid Bahonar University of Kerman

Master's degree, Civil Engineering

Licenses & Certifications

Etabs from Navid Iran - Civil Engineer Issued Jan 2015 - Expires Jan 2017 64752-0063

- B2 SPANISH CFA TORRENT D'EN MELIS
- React + Redux course SoloLearn
- Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3 Coursera
- ADOBE XD Adobe

Skills

Business Strategy • Matlab • Abaqus • SAP • HTML • Finite Element Analysis • Finite Volume • ETABS • Web Programming • Graphic Design